free-online-articles.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy

### Your Privacy:

The privacy of our worthy visitors is our primary motive. To protect your privacy in a suitable way, we efficiently provide you the notice in which our online information is explained very clearly. Not only this, there are given some alternatives as well that you can choose in order to know that how we collect your data and use it. In order to make sure that the notice is visible to you all, we have made it available on the homepage and at the place where the knowledge of the personal identification is required.

#### Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie:

Google acts as the third party advertisement vendor. To serve advertisements on this website, Google utilizes cookies. Furthermore, Google also uses DART cookies, as it allows them to provide the advertisements to the visitors, which are established on their visits on to Free Online Articles or the other websites that are having existence on the World Wide Web. 

If you are looking to pick from the DART cookies, you have to go through the Google advertisement and content network privacy policy, by clicking on <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. The users tracking with the DART cookie are liable to Google’s privacy policies.

The other third party ad servers or advertisement networks further utilize cookies. This helps them in keeping a track of the various activities of the visitors. Free Online Articles has no accountability towards these cookies, as the third party uses these.

#### Personal Data Collection:

With every visit on the Free Online Articles, it means that the IP address visitors use while accessing website is logged with the information like time and date of the accession. The related data is used in order to administer the site, track user’s movement, analyze trends site and collect extensive demographic information for the intrinsic utilization only. An important consideration for you is that no IP address is connected to the personal acknowledgeable data.

#### Third Party Websites:

For the use and reference of visitors, we have attached links at this website, but the Free Online Articles is not responsible at all for the privacy policies of these websites.

#### Changes to this Privacy Statement:

At times, there can be any modification in our policies and Free Online Articles welcomes you at [www.free-online-articles.com](http://www.free-online-articles.com/) for solving your any kind of query regarding privacy policy.
